(Sheldon:)I just want you both to know,
when I publish my findings...
(Sheldon:)-...I won't forget your contributions.
-Great.
(Sheldon:)I can't mention you
in my Nobel acceptance speech.
When I write my memoirs...
(Sheldon:)...you can expect a very effusive footnote
and perhaps a signed copy.
(Raj:)-We have to tell him.
-Tell me what?
(Howard:)Damn his Vulcan hearing.
You are planning a party for me,
aren't you?
(Howard:)Okay, Sheldon, sit down.
(Sheldon:)If there's going to be a theme,
I should let you know...
(Sheldon:)...I don't care for luau, toga
or under the sea.
(Howard:)Yeah. We'll keep that in mind.
Look, we need to talk to you...
(Howard:)...about something that happened
at the North Pole.
(Sheldon:)If this is about the night
the heat went out...
(Sheldon:)...there's nothing
to be embarrassed about.
(Raj:)-It's not about that.
-We agreed to never speak of it again.
(Sheldon:)So we slept together naked.